I'm going to show you a video of what's going on in Gaza.
And then I'm going to show you a video of what's going on in an Israeli city nine miles away.
And if after that, you can still come in the comments and ask me, but what about Hamas?
If you try and throw some like biblical verse at me.
What about the hostages?
Like, it's really scary to realize that you're just surrounded by so many soulless people.
We're going to show you a video of what's going on in Gaza.
To better understand modern day colonialism, I've been keeping up with the everyday lives
of people on the ground in both Israel and the difference in lifestyles is important
to point out during apartheid and especially during times of conflict. It's unfortunate
but the nature of occupation always rears its ugly head. So last night I looked at Nedivat,
Israel which is only nine miles away from Gaza. These are the Instagram stories.
Many of the stories show cheering as each bomb drops in Gaza. We see people working out and
getting their nails or hair done and then that very night cheering on as entire families are
wiped from the map. Unfortunately this behavior is not new. Zionists do this every year. They
have live streaming events and watch parties as the bombs fall on Gaza.